<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Edgar Aranda</title>
    <link>https://earanda.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Edgar Aranda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 21:41:31 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://earanda.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Helpful Commands</title>
      <link>https://earanda.dev/posts/2021/02/hugo-helpful-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 21:41:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://earanda.dev/posts/2021/02/hugo-helpful-commands/</guid>
      <description>Hugo its a very useful framework to build websites in the geekiest way possible but at the same time I consider it very simple (depending on your skill set).
This is a list of the most useful and only commands that I use:

Create a new site
Note: Remember you need to be in the parent folder, it will create the new folder and all the Hugo files inside of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://earanda.dev/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 14:54:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://earanda.dev/projects/</guid>
      <description>Electron  stocks-ticker  React  would-you-rather my-reads  React Native  mobile-flashcards  NodeJS  mysql-lazyrest mta-metro  Jquery  emojiPass  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://earanda.dev/posts/2021/02/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 01:07:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://earanda.dev/posts/2021/02/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>👋 Welcome to my Site This is my first post on what would by my new blog / repository of ideas and Software Engineering ramblings.
I will try to portray my knowledge and experience of 10+ years working from startups to multinational companies, the bad , the good, the tools, the tricks and what ever I have learned in this journey, hopefully this helps you out as it will help me keep track of my thoughts and stop saving stuff all over plus 1K+ bookmarks that I never visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://earanda.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 01:01:01 -0101</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://earanda.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>HI, My name is Edgar, I live in 🗽 and I am a Senior Software Engineer with 10+ years of experience in several technologies, languages, frameworks, and databases. In this past years I have worked with plenty environments, developing tools, methodologies and version control tools for small and multinational teams.
I have profitiently worked in different business areas like retail, e-commerce, security, education, energy and health industries.
My main work collaboration has been in propriertary projects and companies, so its complicated to share a full spectrum of my work experience, but you can find some of my side projects in my projects section.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
