<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Edgar Aranda</title>
    <link>https://earanda.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Edgar Aranda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 01:07:15 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://earanda.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://earanda.dev/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 14:54:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://earanda.dev/projects/</guid>
      <description>Electron  stocks-ticker  React  would-you-rather my-reads  React Native  mobile-flashcards  NodeJS  mysql-lazyrest mta-metro  Jquery  emojiPass  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://earanda.dev/posts/2021/02/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 01:07:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://earanda.dev/posts/2021/02/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Project: This is my first electron App, maybe a little too late regarding on what is the future for electron but I needed a very minimal vertical stocks ticker app.
Important note, the app comes AS-IS , also this was a weekend hack so expect some not tested edge cases.
Modes If the martket is open it will display a small sun and if closed a small moon. This is not just a visual aid, but at day it will create a direct websocket connection to update data and at night it will pull data manually every 30min.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://earanda.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 01:01:01 -0101</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://earanda.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>HI, My name is Edgar, I live in 🗽 and I am a Senior Software Engineer with 10+ years of experience in several technologies, languages, frameworks, and databases. In this past years I have worked with plenty environments, developing tools, methodologies and version control tools for small and multinational teams.
I have profitiently worked in different business areas like retail, e-commerce, security, education, energy and health industries.
My main work collaboration has been in propriertary projects and companies, so its complicated to share a full spectrum of my work experience, but you can find some of my side projects in my projects section.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
